switchads.com 2016-04-21

# Privacy and cookie policy| SwitchAds

[Home](http://www.switchads.com/) __ Privacy and cookie policy

SwitchAds is a trading division of Switch Concepts Ltd, a company registered in England and Wales under Company No. 06706037 with a registered address at 37 Commercial Road, Poole, BH14 0HU.

SwitchAds trading address is Hounsdown House, Hounsdown Business Park, Southampton, SO40 9LX.

You can contact us via post to the above address, via email using contact@switchads.com or telephone using 0333 200 1230.

**1\. Introduction**

SwitchAds is committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide us and non-personal information we collect.

This Privacy Policy will explain the following:  
•The difference between personal and non-personal information  
•How your information is collected  
•Your choices regarding the information you have provided to us  
•How we use your information

**2\. What information is collected?**

Personal Information

If you contact us via the website (www.switchads.com) you will be asked to provide personal information such as name, e-mail address and telephone number. This information is provided on a voluntary basis.

Non-personal Information

SwitchAds works with Google Analytics and LeadLander. We track which pages a user visits and to monitor which countries users come from. Cookies are used in these processes. Both of these methods of collecting data are non-personal. The data we collect is anonymous. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please do not use this website.

**3\. How is my information used?**

Personal Information

This information will be used internally to contact you, as requested. Your details will also be added to our database to ensure that we can continue to contact you to deal with your enquiry. We do not share personal information with third parties. In the instances where we propose to use your personal information for other uses, such as promotional communications, then we will ensure that we notify you first and gain your permission. You will be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for the use of your personal information at this point. Should we form a service level agreement with you this privacy policy will be superseded.  
Non-personal Information

We use non-personal information to improve the services we provide by monitoring how users interact with our website.

**4\. How secure is my information?**

At all times we have security measures and technical safeguards in place to prevent unauthorised access, theft or loss of any personal or non-personal information, from both inside and outside our company. Our employees are aware of and accountable for compliance with these procedures.

**5\. Further information and changes to this policy**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy then please contact us at the address listed in the preamble to this policy or using contact@switchads.com

**6\. Company and data protection information**

Switch Concepts Ltd is registered in England and Wales under Company No. 06706037.

Registered address is 37 Commercial Road, Poole, BH14 0HU.

## Cookie policy

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. Most websites you visit will use cookies in order to improve your user experience by enabling that website to ‘remember’ you, either for the duration of your visit (using a ‘session cookie’) or for repeat visits (using a ‘persistent cookie’). Cookies do lots of different jobs like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, supporting functionality such as social sharing, and capturing information about the usage of the website so we can make ongoing improvements.

Our cookies do not store any sensitive or confidential information.

The vast majority of web browsers accept cookies unless you decline them by modifying your browser settings. If you do this please be aware that restricting or deleting cookies may impact on the functionality of the website. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies.

A list of the cookies the website uses follows:

### Third party cookies

**Google Analytics**

_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz

These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site and last for 30 mins to 2 years. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. Please note this cookie may have already been set at an earlier visit.

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
